[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Management is:?",
    "answers": [
      "the art of leading an organization to ensure its proper functioning",
      "the art of advising leaders",
      "The art of selling goods and servicesThe art of selling goods and services"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "the art of leading an organization to ensure its proper functioning."
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Management includes 4 functions:",
    "answers": [
      "pilot / organize / direct / animate and mobilize",
      "Communicate / Organize / Lead / Animate and Mobilize"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "pilot / organize / direct / Animate and mobilize"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Strategic management is part of",
    "answers": ["the short term", "the medium term", "the long term"],
    "correctAnswer": "the long term"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Strategic decisions are?",
    "answers": [
      "easily reversible",
      "difficult to reverse.",
      "In telemedicine, autonomous driving, machine translation."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "difficult to reverse"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Operational management concerns:?",
    "answers": [
      "the short term / medium term",
      " the medium term ",
      "The short term"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "the short term / medium term"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "A contingency factor are:?",
    "answers": [
      "internal and/or external elements to be taken into account as they may influence the decisions and actions of the organisation",
      "people inside/outside the organization"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "internal and/or external elements to be taken into account as they can influence the decisions and actions of the organization"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Check the contingency factors that may be internal to the organization:?",
    "answers": [" The size", " The growth of the country.", "The environment"],
    "correctAnswer": "The size"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Check the contingency factors that may be external to the organization:",
    "answers": ["environment", "age", "size of organization"],
    "correctAnswer": "the environment"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "CSR means: ?",
    "answers": [
      "Corporate Social Responsibility",
      "Environmental Social Responsibility",
      "Societal Resources of the Environment"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Corporate Social Responsibility"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "The stakeholders are:?",
    "answers": [
      "all internal and external actors who can directly or indirectly influence the decisions and actions of the organization",
      "all internal and external elements that can directly or directly influence the decisions and actions of the organization"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "all internal and external actors who can directly or indirectly influence the decisions and actions of the organization"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Internal stakeholders are:",
    "answers": [
      "Employees / suppliers / Bank",
      "Bank / employees / owners",
      "employees / owners / management"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "employees / owners / management"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "An emerging strategy is a strategy: ?",
    "answers": [
      "modifying the initial strategy and being necessary in the face of changes in the environment",
      "planned and planned in advance"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "modifying the initial strategy and being necessary in the face of changes in the environment"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "The management of production in high flows consists of:",
    "answers": [
      "forecasting demand and producing",
      "produce according to orders received"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "forecast demand and produce"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Just-in-time production consists of:?",
    "answers": [
      "produce according to demand forecast",
      "produce according to orders received"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "produce according to orders received"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Production outsourcing consists of:?",
    "answers": [
      "entrust the production that was done to another company",
      "produce yourself"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "entrust the production that was done to another company"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "Quality is a major issue because:?",
    "answers": [
      "it makes it possible to satisfy customers",
      "It makes it possible to collect information"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "it satisfies customers"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "The principles of Taylorism are:?",
    "answers": [
      "horizontal division of labour / vertical division of labour / performance pay",
      "Job enrichment / autonomy / versatility"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "horizontal division of labour / division of labour vertical / pay for performance"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "A rigid organization of work can be characterized by:?",
    "answers": ["a specialisation of employees", "Employee autonomy"],
    "correctAnswer": "employee autonomy"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Direct supervision is a coordination mechanism:?",
    "answers": [
      "where a leader decides and controls",
      "where members adjust through informal communication"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "where a leader decides and controls"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "The decentralization of power is characterized by:?",
    "answers": [
      "power distributed in several hands",
      "a power held by a person"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "a power distributed in several hands"
  }
]
